#OP
#ED
#Insert
#Signs
Afternoon, everyone!
Tomorrow starts your long awaited summer vacation!
Those of you who are going to the ocean, mountains,
rivers, valleys, and PriPara,
make sure to fully enjoy your youth,
and deepen your friendships!
However!
Remember to do your homework!
You'd better not forget about it!
That's all. Dismissed!
It's summer vacation!
Let's have lots of fun this summer, Nao!
We definitely will!
And I can even go to PriPara with you this year!
That's right!
We'll go to PriPara, and the pool,
and PriPara, and the pool, and PriPara, and the pool...
Um... What about our homework?
Miss Midorikaze.
Even though you're starting summer vacation,
we'll be continuing with the
Princess lessons every day as per usual.
Give it your all.
Of course, I'll do my best!
Fuwari sure is fired up!
My Prince, a Goat, a Date, and Me
A Date with Prince and the Goat.
And a un, deux, trois.
Un, deux, trois.
Elegant and beautiful...
The world is my oyster.
I'll rise to the top.
A dazzling, gorgeous and noble princess!
And to do that requires heart, technique, and physique.
You must wholeheartedly become a princess!
It seems you still have a long way to go.
However, compared to when you started,
you've made a lot of progress.
Thank you very much, Ms. Gloria.
I'm being tough on you since
I want you to win the Grand Prix.
Grand Prix?
With whom should I form a five person team, I wonder?
I'm sure Prince Hibiki is figuring that out.
Anyway, that is all for today's lesson.
After this, you should practice what we've worked on today.
Thank you very much.
Now then, have a nice day.
Unacceptable!
We're here to determine the additional
two members who will join us...
in the Summer Dream Idol Grand Prix-pri!
First, we've already agreed on Fuwari.
We haven't asked her yet, though.
Laala, we'll leave that to you-kuma.
It seems you're the one who talks to her the most-kuma.
Capisce!
The other could be...
Kyupikon!
...Nanami!
I don't think so-pri.
Iroha already turned us down...
That girl?
The one we put on a passionate concert with that one time?
Didn't she join with New & Mew and that other girl?
They're already of one mind and body.
One mind and body
I guess this time we'll try leaving it to our manager.
Usa?
We've already decided on Fuwari, but...
Go find someone for us.
Someone who is super skilled who'll join us and win.
Usa!
You say that, but with how much I've been
tending to Dressing Pafé recently,
I've had no motivation to go out scouting-usa.
It's a manager's job to scout others-usa!
But to find someone who can win...
We have no choice but to bring
someone in from outside PriPara.
Whoa, we can do something like that?!
Impossible-usa.
As I'm sure you can tell,
I don't have that many connections-usa.
That's true.
Elegant and beautiful.
The world is my oyster.
I will rise to the top.
And become a radiant, gorgeous, and noble princess!
That's wonderful-tori!
Toriko saw a dazzling princess-tori!
Compared to Fuwari, Toriko is a plain, worthless, overshadowed piece of rubbish.
Hey, Toriko,
I wonder what "rise to the top" actually means.
It means that everyone else is below you-tori.
You'd be a princess that will stand at the top-tori.
Compared to that, Toriko is a plain,
worthless, overshadowed piece of rubbish...
Isn't that lonely?
Tori?
Wouldn't it be lonely to stand above everyone else?
I want to be with everyone...
But Fuwari, you wouldn't be a princess-tori!
My prince's Making Drama is truly wonderful.
I sparkle and shine...
But I'm not understanding it any better.
I wonder if it's the right fit for me.
Huh? Why?
Well...
Wait, did you just speak like a human?!
Laala, why are you at school?
I came because I wanted to ask you to join our Dream Team.
Ah! Why are you here, Laala?!
Dorothy.
You're trying to get the jump on us!
It's like I keep saying, Fuwari's joining Dressing Pafé, right?
Huh?! But I want her to join SoLaMi Smile!
Not happening.
I mean, having the princess candidate
join your team would be a cheap way to win.
Same goes to you!
Nuh-uh, we're totally different.
How are you different?
I wonder if I can even become the princess.
Huh?
So Shikyouin gave you a Making Drama as a present.
Yeah.
However, it's not going well.
Something like the "world is my oyster"
doesn't really seem like me.
Huh? Why?
Well, "the world is my oyster"
is something I'm max down with.
I do have the qualities of a princess, you know.
Dorothy...
Maybe someone more suitable like
Dorothy should be the princess.
Really?
Then let's go talk to Shikyouin.
I don't think that's what she meant...
All right, Hibiki, give us a sharp gaze.
Yeah, that's great. Show us some more emotion!
Yes, that'll do!
Great!
Yeah!
All right. Thank you, everyone.
We're done for the day.
You did well.
Thanks.
What is it?
Ah, I see.
Got it.
The world is my oyster....
My prince!
I'm sorry I'm so busy and can't see you more often.
Could these roses possibly be
enough to beg your forgiveness?
Um...
I forgive you.
Your lack of sentence-enders cleanses the heart.
The one who knows not of uncleanliness,
with a heart of pure white,
and is the ideal princess candidate,
would you go on a date with me?
Hold on tight.
Okay!
Let's perform the Making Drama I gave you.
It's beautiful!
Is this really me?
A beautiful dress befitting of a beautiful princess.
And to top it off...
Wow!
Delicious!
Bon appétit!
This is the spoon you use for dessert.
R-Right.
Beautiful.
Huh?!
Your smile is like the summer sun,
sparkling through the trees.
Look...
You're so radiant, even the lobster is blushing!
See?
Beautiful girl...
May I have this dance?
I'd love to.
They're beautiful.
Stunning.
This step...
This sense of rhythm...
Look how good you are.
Could I...
really be?
I've been lonely.
As I am known as a prince in this glamorous world,
all the women who approach me are but mere shams.
Ah, how love's tender touch has escaped my grasp!
As have the roses of passion!
But I have found them at last.
Take my hand and become the true princess!
I'm looking forward to your concert tomorrow, Fuwari.
Show me the you who has been dyed in my colour.
I will.
Keep them balanced.
Stand up straight.
That's right.
You're doing wonderful.
Do your feet hurt?
You're not even going to take them off during your break?
No!
A princess must always wear elegant footwear.
Elegant and beautiful...
The world is my oyster.
I will rise above everyone else.
Illuminate the world, gorgeous noble princess!
The world is my oyster!
Wholeheartedly become a princess.
The world is my oyster...
That isn't wholehearted...
Someone tell me what I should do!
Capisce.
Laala?
I'm here again.
Um... What should I tell you?
I came here to become a princess, yet...
Laala, what should I do?
Um...
Th-That's pretty difficult.
I'm not sure, sorry.
I see.
Well, if you're not sure what to do,
why don't you blow it away?
Blow it away?
Yeah.
If you put everything into exercising,
and just concentrate on having fun,
eventually you'll be like
"Huh? What was I even worried about?"
That sounds wonderful!
Hey! Laala's trying to get the jump on us again!
Dorothy, relax.
Dressing Pafé!
Let's all go play together.
Huh?
What's gotten into you suddenly?
With the Summer Dream so close, we don't have the ti—
The Daruma has fallen over!
Laala has fallen over!
Max capisce!
Capisce!
Mirei has fallen over!
Gotcha!
Gotcha...
You moved, Dorothy!
No I didn't!
You did too!
Did not!
Relax you two.
You did!
Did not!
Stop right there!
Why you!
Leona, this way!
If you want to go that way, Dorothy...
Fuwari, let's go that way!
Oh, okay!
Look out! I'm gonna catch you!
Got ya!
Stop!
Capisce catch!
Now you're it, Fuwari.
Oh, okay!
Is it okay if I take you off for a little, shoes?
Fuwari!
Over here!
I'll get you!
Hold it!
Wait up!
She's fast!
Whoa!
Huh?
You all came?
Let's race!
We climbed a tree together the first time I met you.
We did.
Ever since then, I've always thought that...
being with you is a lot of fun.
Ever since then?
Yeah.
Ever since we first met.
You're far more fascinating now than when we first met.
Is that true?
What are those two doing?
I'm not sure.
Oh no. I forgot to practice.
From Fuwari?
Please scan the appropriate number of My Tickets for your coord.
Coord Change Start!
A coord that represents the clear water
and blue skies in the Palps.
It's a coord that Mother Nature would love.
Palps Sky Country Coord!
I'm sorry, but please wait just a little longer.
Making Drama Switch On!
Let's go!
A mysterious spring orchestra!
Cyalume Change!
You're awesome, Fuwari!
You really are!
Fuwari did really good.
Yeah, it was super cute.
I want her in SoLaMi Smile more and more-pri.
That's right.
I'm counting on you.
I am unaccustomed to waiting.
We'll need to take drastic measures with the princess.
I wonder if I upset him.
Next episode
Celebrity 4?
What's that?
It's a group of four top idols that my prince called to form a dream team with me.
Cera.
Leika.
Britney.
Tyna.
We're Celebrity 4!
Gorgeous!
What? No way!
Even if you try to strong-arm us, we won't give up Fuwari!
Next time:
Run! SummDrea GrandPrix!
Run!  SummDrea GrandPrix
Aim for your dreams!
Let's go PriPara!